{
    "id": "39cef57145e24031a00726948d590b76",
    "title": "Already and yet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "09549a08a98e40109cddcbbd74e46fcb",
            "title": "Already And Yet",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She has not ………………… started working on the project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………….. sent the payment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "As …………………, I haven’t had time to talk to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have …………………. finished.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was tired, ………………….. he didn’t give up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The invitees have ………………….. turned up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was surprised that they had ………………….. finished the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "already",
                        "yet"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was surprised that she had ………………….. to start working on that project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government has …………………. to approve the project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ………………… had enough.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}